{
    "subject": "Archduchess_Theresa_of_Austria__b._1931_",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Prince_Rasso_of_Bavaria",
    "human_readable": "Archduchess Theresa of Austria, born in 1931, is married to Prince Rasso of Bavaria.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9473292231559753,
            "question": "Who is Archduchess Theresa of Austria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9267556071281433,
            "question": "When was Archduchess Theresa of Austria born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9187164902687073,
            "question": "Who is Prince Rasso of Bavaria married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.831590473651886,
            "question": "Is Archduchess Theresa a member of the Austrian royal family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8004510998725891,
            "question": "What year did Archduchess Theresa get married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7641147971153259,
            "question": "Is Archduchess Theresa a member of the Bavarian royal family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7178691625595093,
            "question": "What is the name of Archduchess Theresa's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6229037046432495,
            "question": "What is the name of Archduchess Theresa's husband's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6075140833854675,
            "question": "Which European country are both Archduchess Theresa and Prince Rasso from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5840824842453003,
            "question": "To which royal family does Archduchess Theresa belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Archduchess Theresa of Austria, born in 1931, is married to Prince Rasso of Bavaria.",
            "html": "yago_18059_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which European country are both Archduchess Theresa and Prince Rasso from?",
            "html": "yago_18059_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Archduchess Theresa's husband's family?",
            "html": "yago_18059_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Archduchess Theresa's spouse?",
            "html": "yago_18059_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18059_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18059_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18059_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18059_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18059_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18059_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18059_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18059_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18059_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_18059_90.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that Archduchess Theresa of Austria was born in 1931 and is married to Prince Rasso of Bavaria."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}